cubics.com 2013-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Cubics

THE CUBICS SOCIAL NETWORK CHANNEL PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME. 

PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES.

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how information, including but not limited to personally identifiable information, you voluntarily provide, authorize to be released, or which is publicly available may be obtained and used for purposes of marketing by Adknowledge, Inc. and its Cubics social network advertising operations (together referred to herein as “Cubics”). Cubics is a technology company displaying advertisements through businesses which have contracted with Cubics to consumers who have voluntarily registered with Cubics or one of its partners, or through third party Websites, social networking applications and other means (together, these third party sources are referenced hereafter as “Publishers”). As used herein, “online” means using the Internet, including Websites and related technologies and “offline” means methods other than online, including in person, via postal mail, telephone and similar means. This Policy does not apply to the practices of Publishers or other companies that Cubics does not own or control or to people that Cubics does not employ or manage. Cubics retains its right to modify this policy from time to time by re-publishing it on the Internet; please check back for updates, as reflected in the “Effective as of” date above. Further, Cubics retains its right to enter into new or different lines of business with consumers and, if and to the extent it does so, may display a different Privacy Policy to the consumer for such lines of business.

1\. Collection of Information.

1.1 Subscription or Survey Information. Cubics collects information from you when you voluntarily provide it to Cubics or one of its Publishers (for example, by signing up for an email newsletter or through a co-registration offer on a survey), or by others means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a “User Form”). In a User Form, Cubics or a third party may offer you incentives in exchange for providing information about yourself such as name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, employment information, and personal and online interests (together, “User Information”). Completing the Surveys is voluntary and you are under no obligation to provide User Information.

1.2 Vendor List Information. Cubics may obtain information about you after you provide information to a third party and you permit that party (the “Seller”) to share the information, which Cubics subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise lawfully acquires. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education, marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and other information which you provided to the Seller (together, “Vendor List Information”). When acquiring Vendor List Information, Cubics requires assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Vendor List Information to Cubics and that Cubics may lawfully use the Vendor List Information to transmit offers from advertisers.

1.3 User Behaviors Collected with Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Technology and Information. Cubics uses cookie and web beacon technology to collect and associate certain Internet-related information about you, such as your Internet Protocol address and what Web browser you are using, with certain of your online behaviors, such as viewing or clicking on a particular online advertisement in order to provide you more relevant ads. Additionally, Cubics may use other new and evolving sources of information and information gathering in the future (together, “Technology Information”).

(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows Cubics to identify your Web browser with corresponding information in Cubics’ database. Cubics may use cookies to track individual responses or views of advertisements. You may read more about cookies at [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

(b) Web beacons. A web beacon is programming code used to display an image on a web page or in an email and can also transfer an individual’s user identification, such as IP address and Web browser, to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about the individual. Web beacons enable Cubics to track certain Web sites you visit or advertisements you view online. Web beacons help determine products or services in which you may be interested and help track online behaviors for marketing purposes. More information about web beacons is available at <http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html>.

(c) Where Technology Information is Collected. Technology Information is collected directly from Cubics advertisements or indirectly through Publishers that Cubics contracts with to display advertisements. Such advertisements will usually be displayed within one of the following advertising vehicles:

Websites. Cubics may set a cookie on your computer when you view advertisements delivered on Publisher Websites. After a cookie is set, Cubics may track how you interact with the advertisement and the Publisher Website (for example, registering, purchasing, browsing, etc.) through the use of Web beacons.

Software Programs. Similar to Websites, Cubics displays banner advertisements in software programs and applications that you may use.

Email Databases. Cubics may track your interaction with email advertisements sent to you on behalf of Publishers or partner Websites (for example, when you register, purchase, or browse in response to such email).

1.4 Outside Information. Cubics may lawfully receive information about you from third parties, such as information located in public databases (“Outside Information”).

1.5 No Information Collected from Minors. MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 18 SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO CUBICS. If Cubics is notified it has personal information about a minor under the age of 18, that information will be promptly deleted from our database.

1.6 Individual Information. As used herein, Individual Information means User Information, Vendor List Information, Technology Information, Outside Information, and any other information Cubics lawfully obtains about you.

2\. Use of Individual Information and User Data.

2.1 Discretion to Use Information. Information voluntarily provided to Cubics or lawfully obtained by Cubics is the property of Cubics and may be used by Cubics for any lawful purpose, including for marketing purposes. If you wish to end your email subscription with us or one of our Publishers, you may follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe or follow the instructions detailed at Section 4 below.

2.2 Targeted Advertising and Information. Cubics uses Individual Information to target advertising and other information, such as business, weather, entertainment, sports and general news alerts and similar information, more effectively. When an individual is online, Cubics uses Technology Information to associate an individual with their Individual Information and Cubics attempts to show information and advertising for products and services to which the person may respond. Cubics may use data collected from a response to one type of advertising or information for targeting advertisements or other information through a different venue. For example, Cubics may notice that you responded to a baseball banner advertisement and use that response to deliver a baseball-related advertisement and other information to you.

2.3 Legal Process. Cubics may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders and other legal process as required by law.

2.4 Summary Data. Cubics may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

2.5 Storage of Individual Information. Cubics stores and maintains Individual Information in a database on Cubics computers. Some Individual Information may also be stored by Cubics’ Publishers on the Publishers’ computers. In addition, Cubics’ computers have security measures, such as a firewall, to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Cubics’ control. Cubics also maintains physical and procedural safeguards to protect Individual Information. Notwithstanding such measures, Cubics cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent these computers from being illegally accessed and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

2.6 Business Transition. Cubics may transfer all or part of your Individual Information as part of a business transition such as a merger, acquisition, or asset sale.

3\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

3.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Publishers who place advertisements on the Internet may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to collect information about you. Cubics does not control Publishers’ use of such technology.

3.2 Links. The Publishers’ Website and email messages transmitted by Cubics on its own behalf or on behalf of Publishers may contain hypertext links to the Websites of third parties. Cubics is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

3.3 Affiliated Companies that are not Publishers. Cubics may disclose or transfer Individual Information to wholly owned or controlled Cubics entities in Cubics’ discretion.

4\. HOW YOU MAY EXERCISE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS AND OPT OUT OR UNSUBSCRIBE.

4.1 Websites. To prevent the display of Publisher or Cubics advertising on a Website, for example banner advertisements, do not visit the Website. To stop being shown ads personalized to your interests from Cubics or its Publishers, please visit our [Opt-Out Page](http://up.bidsystem.com/adfeedback.php) by clicking [here](http://up.bidsystem.com/adfeedback.php). Please note that opting out does not mean you will stop receiving ads or will see fewer ads online; it means the ads you do see through or from Cubics or its Publishers will not be personalized to your interests. In order to honor your preference to stop the display of ads recommended by or through our technology, Cubics will drop a do-not-track cookie on your computer labeled “ADKOO” and will not show you personalized ads as long as you do not delete that cookie.

4.2 Software Programs. To prevent software programs from displaying advertisements on your computer, uninstall the Software Program provided through Cubics or a Publisher by following the instructions included in the privacy policy at the time of installation. Software Programs should include an option to uninstall in the “Add/Remove Programs” section of the Windows® operating system, or by visiting the file director of the installed program and running an uninstaller executable.

5\. More Information.

5.1 For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit [http://www.netcoalition.com](http://www.netcoalition.com/) and [http://www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/). To learn more about online behavioral advertising and your privacy choices, you may wish to visit<http://www.aboutads.info/consumers>. Cubics reserves the right to update this Policy at any time by republishing it to this Website with a new effective date. If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at [privacy@adknowledge.com](mailto:privacy@adknowledge.com?Subject=Questions%20about%20Adknowledge%20Privacy%20Policy) or write to us at:

Cubics  
Attn: General Counsel  
4600 Madison Ave., 10th Floor  
Kansas City, MO 64112
